ipocentral.in 2019-07-31

# Privacy Policy – IPO Central

IPO Central (“IPO Central“) operates IPO Central.com and may operate other websites. It is IPO Central’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

 **Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, IPO Central collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. IPO Central’s intent for doing so is to be well acquainted with how its visitors use its website. From time to time, IPO Central may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

IPO Central also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on IPO Central.com. IPO Central only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.

 **Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

to gather personally identifying information. The amount and type of information that IPO Central gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at IPO Central.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with IPO Central are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, IPO Central collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with IPO Central. Disclose personally identifying other than as described below. Supply personally identifying, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

 **Aggregated Statistics**

IPO Central may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. IPO Central may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, IPO Central does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

 **Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

IPO Central discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on IPO Central behalf or to provide services available at IPO Central websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using IPO Central websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. IPO Central will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, IPO Central discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when IPO Central believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of IPO Central, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an IPO Central website and have supplied your email address, IPO Central may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with IPO Central and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. IPO Central takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

 **Log Files and Cookies**

This website utilizes industry standard analytics packages which gathers limited information on visitors to our website automatically, and stores this anonymous information in server log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, basic IP information, referring pages, operating system used and date/time stamps. This information does not identify individual users; it is used only for site administration, as well as for analysis of website usage and trends.

Additionally, cookies may be used to provide easier and faster access to website features such as logins and/or repeat visits. Cookies are very small text files that are stored on personal computers for reference purposes. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally indentifiable information you have submitted while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when your browser is closed, and a persistent cookie may stay on your hard drive for an extended period. Session cookies make it easier for you to navigate our site; persistent cookies can perform such activities as storing your password for forums or blogs so you do not have to sign in every time you visit those areas, and/or may be used to enable us to track and target the interests of our users so as to enhance the overall experience of using our site.

We have no access to or administration abilities over any cookies that are used by any advertisers on our site.

 **Business Transfers**

If IPO Central, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that IPO Central goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of IPO Central may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

 **Ads**

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by IPO Central and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

 **Privacy Policy Changes**

From time to time, and in IPO Central’s sole discretion.IPO Central encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have an IPO Central.com account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
